preview of the next meeting
Three corps commanders will stand up this time and call for members by draft nomination.
Play various games with the new members.
The winning team will each receive a bottle of raw yakiniku pork belly!
The winner will receive a fresh BBQ pork belly and a pork belly with a fresh meat filling.
The group will continue the game of association.
The team with the most correct answers out of the 5 questions will get 4 points.
Now it's on to the challenge of the Mayutan Association, which is currently in third place.
The Mayutan Association is now overwhelmingly last.
We're by far the worst.
We're the last.
I see.
Please don't make it sound like I'm not satisfied.
Okay, let's play the pose-association game.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four.
Three, four, three, two, one.
Look at that.
What's that one?
Here are your answers.
Zoo.
Wow!
That's right.
Then touch it.
How did you know that?
I'm good at this.
I'm good at taking a drink.
What were you doing?
Elephant.
I was doing bears.
I don't understand.
What's this?
It's a lion.
A lion?
Lion, this ain't no lion.
No, you don't understand.
That's awesome.
That's great.
Okay, here we go.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
Stop.
That's disgusting.
What is this?
It's not good...
Guess what it is.
What is this?
Let's read it, read it, read it, read it
Oh, thank you!
Oh, that's close!
It's hard...
Well, well, well, this is a Hatsumode, isn't it?
What was written here?
What?
I told Mikku to do Hatsuhinode.
I told him.
It was the first sunrise of the year.
I thought he was eating something.
I told him to give me instructions.
Someone didn't tell me what to do.
What were you doing?
I was eating rice cakes.
You were eating something.
What were you doing?
I was warming myself on the kotatsu.
I don't get it.
I don't know.
Okay, here we go.
Ten.
I love you.
Nine.
Eight.
Six.
Stop. Stop.
Yes, you can watch.
Please don't move.
Mimikin's cute.
Okay? Okay, here's your answer.
Evolution?
Hmm? Evolutionary chart?
Evolution? Human.
No, sir!
Oh, no! No!
It's a roller coaster.
You're too smart for that.
Yeah, it's gonna be an evolutionary chart.
I don't get that.
Evolutionary chart.
I only guessed one question!
What are you doing, Maeda Association?
Good luck with that...
Here we go.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
What's this?
Basketball.
Yes. Correct.
You're good at this.
Was that easy to do?
Was that easy?
Let's get the next one out.
Here are your answers.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
Okay, stop.
Okay, you can look.
What are you doing?
Stop, please.
Can I...
What?
Ikeda, stop, please.
Come on, let's go.
Please. Go ahead.
Bungy.
No, no, no.
It's a circus.
What were you doing?
Walking the tightrope.
Oh, tightrope walking.
What's with the poses?
Do they all look alike?
Statue bending.
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it.
I don't even know what you're talking about.
Like the trapeze.
Why don't we all do the trapeze?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The three of us.
How?
I told you to do it with the receiver.
Hey...
Yeah?
I don't know what it is, but...
I don't know.
I don't know...
eh?
I don't know.
I don't know I don't know
I don't know
I don't know! I don't know!
You don't know what you're talking about!
I don't give a fuck! I don't give a fuck!
Fuck you!
Buber, then the four Seths take on the neck challenge.
How confident are you that your necks are long and powerful, but you seem to be able to judge them calmly, and they seem to line up properly here, while the rest of the group is just sitting there, looking like a bunch of pussies.
The rest of the group was a mess... and Eroko is keeping it quiet...
I like it here.
I'm getting compliments on my part.
Now then, I'd like you to get down on your face... and break your long necks.
I'll turn it over to you.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
I'm not moving.
Yes, it's stuck.
Read it, read it, read it.
I got it.
Wedding
I see what you mean.
It looked like a wedding.
Oh, my God.
That's nice.
Okay, here we go.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
Stop, stop, stop.
Yes, sir.
Oh, here we go.
Campfire.
Yeah!
There it is.
What a campfire campfire such a high thing looked a bit like coffee
I thought you liked it when you said that.
Maybe I do.
Then what are you gonna do with the marshmallows or something?
What are you doing?
What are you talking about?
Okay, change of plans.
I'm going to change the subject... this way.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven. - Six.
Six. - Five.
One.
Stop, please.
This is hard.
What's this?
Wait a minute.
Read it, read it, read it.
What's this?
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, read it.
It's about time.
Okay, here's the answer.
Sento.
Sento (public bathhouse) is fine.
People in a public bathhouse.
Oh, no.
I'll ruin it.
What was that about Yumiki at first?
It's like...
It's a hot spring.
Like she wants to do it.
I don't know. I don't think I can do it.
I don't think I can do it.
He's telling me to stop.
Sit down.
Let's see what we've got here.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
Yay!
Good luck.
Take a good look at each one.
You're amazing.
You don't have to look at one of them.
Get it together, get it together, get it together.
Wow, I have no idea what this is.
Okay, I'm ready for some answers now.
Baseball.
Baseball, please.
Nice try.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I'm Picopin.
Oh, Dekopin!
Why are you playing Decopin?
I don't know why you do it.
Why are you playing Dekopin?
Because lately, when I run away from the world, it's always with Decopin.
What did you think it was?
No, I really don't know... that's why they're like eyes.
Because I can't see them in my dreams.
Nice fight.
So far, you've only answered one question correctly.
Can you get the last one?
I can't get it.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Yes, stop.
Stop! Stop! Stop!
What is she doing?
Come on.
What?
Wait a minute, I have no idea.
You won.
What do I do?
Come on, please. Come on.
Reptile Cafe.
What a shame.
Iyoki, what are you doing?
They pushed me into this crop.
Say "ahhh".
I'm the one who's doing it, but you should do it.
You'd better play, like, "Effree" or something.
Who's the other guy?
That's right.
I only got one right.
Let's tell the leader!
Let's have a showdown.
The four players, except the leader, will each think of a word associated with the theme and announce it in turn.
The leader will try to find the correct answer to the question by the second clue.
First, the last member of the corps is nominated. Who will be chosen?
Sakura Kawasaki.
I like it here... you've been doing a lot better than the three-way recently.
Are you going to poke it in?
No, I'm not.
She thinks you're trying to get in her head.
What kind of a rush do you think I'm getting?
I was eating something oily the other night.
You're a monster for eating oily food.
I said, "What are you eating? I said, "Oil-based food.
I see...
Which is which?
First of all, which is which?
That's terrible, isn't it?
Chikatsuki-san was eating.
He told me it's hot.
He said, "It's kind of hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
What's the point of this?
I mean, what was he talking about in the first place?
Come on...
First laundry hopefuls
Mayu-tan Association
Aya Ogawa
Oh!
Ogawa
Aya
Ogawa is a guy.
I'm sure we'll be able to work together...
I'm sure everyone will heal you.
I'm sure he'll heal one more person.
I'm sure he'll heal you.
That's amazing.
You're all regulated, aren't you?
Yes, we did.
Let's go.
The first player who wants to do laundry.
Mr. Kaibu.
It's Tadasokun.
what is it?
Hayashi
Oh Hayashi
Hayashi.
Very nice.
Oh, Hayashi? Why?
Before...
You said you didn't have any friends and that you wanted one.
He said he wanted to be a friend. He said he had a friend when he was doing the B-News.
But, well, some people think that's a lie.
Before the last game, the three corps are finally completed. First of all, let's challenge Kaede-san!
Yes, yes...
This is the important part, the last game. I wanted to get tongs for sure.
I love yakiniku too, so when we win, I'll bring the tongs to the barbecue with everyone.
It took a lot of courage.
I think it's better to do it alone.
So, I announced the theme to the four of us.
Without consulting each other, we came up with an associative clue.
Can you give it to the leader Sato more quickly?
That's right.
Go ahead, first person.
If you answer just this one, you get 4 points.
Let's use only these clues.
"Haunted house"?
No, it's not.
Now open the second one.
Go ahead.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, I think I got it.
Okay, I got it.
Here we go.
A haunted place.
Eh...
Come on, open the third one
Suspension bridge effect
If we put this out here, we won't be seen by anyone.
I see.
Let's go.
Let's test our mettle.
Oh!
That's right.
Oh, great.
I see you've come up with these three.
Good boy!
I honestly didn't understand the fishing bridge effect at all.
The only option left was a test of courage.
I see...
It looked like your boyfriend played an active role, but I guess not.
Oh no...
Tomisato and by the way...
That's right.
I'm
The Soul of Fire.
The spirit of fire
That ball of fire.
I'm just a ball of fire.
I hope I got this one right the first time.
Last two.
Switching the clue members, the second question
Can you think of an exquisite word that Sato will understand?
First of all, let's open up the word associations.
Sky Tree
534m Musashi
Wow!
Nakanishi, me...
Oh, I got it!
I got one... but I already got one.
Okay. That's good.
We'll change the subject for the third question.
The first person to get a clear round is pretty close to the winner...
Let's go to the first word association.
"Open.
"Work.
Let's see if you can catch it with this one.
Idol.
No, no, no. Come on, Tomisato, the second one.
The first one.
Work
Come on, let's answer.
Salaryman.
Salaryman, no.
Come on, Lin, let's go to the third one.
Apple.
Come on, please answer.
Eron Musk. - Eron Musk.
Eron Musk, no.
Matsuo.
Work.
Come on.
That's great.
Oh, that's great.
Come on, squeeze it out.
Macbook.
Oh, oh, oh.
What's that? That's a close one.
Nice try. The correct answer is
PC
Ohhhhhh
that's too close
Finally, the last problem. Kuroki boating Sato.
When you get to the third clue...
Cookie?
Cookie.
What's that?
Last Nakanishi, please.
Manatsu-san.
Manatsu-san, you just came out and froze.
Let's go.
Here they come. Over.
Macarons!
Correct, yes.
This one was hard, but... but... you figured it out with that clue.
You say I've made up for it, but I haven't, because you're just too good.
We'll tell the leader that we're going to confront him, followed by a survey of the Kublinses, and since the score is probably stuck, we'll have to get it right.
I'm not sure I'm ready to be a corps leader yet... but I'll feel more confident if I can understand everyone here.
I don't have confidence yet because I've only been with the corps for a few minutes.
The first question is, can the four of you tell the corps leader the answer?
Here we go.
First one's open.
That's a wide range.
Mike.
Why Mike?
Come on, Yang-Ki, open.
Sparkle, please answer me.
Nogizaka46
Why?
Come on, third one, Tsutsui, open.
Okay, I got it.
Here you go.
Idol
The second one is also a good month too much... too much time... The second one is also a low-calorie information type clue...
Western-style house
I'm hoping to get a high score for the third question in the clinches.
Now, let's open the associative word!
Let's go, Yumiki, and get 4 points if you guess right here.
Ms. Dyan
You've got it.
Let's go to Kawasaki.
Bananaman.
That's our name.
Here you go.
Groomin'.
Laughing is all in the first shot, right?
Come on, Fukuda, open!
Set
Ah, Nogizaka Tsumekizaka
Too bad
Here we go to the end, Youki Open
Ent.
Banana's Ent.
Let's have him answer. Go ahead.
Imoowalizer is on. - Why our names?
Why our names?
Why is it our name?
You're the one who came up with it. You're one of the many people who got it right.
No, that one.
Kawasaki, you named it after us.
Thank you.
You're the closest comedian I've ever met.
Thank you very much.
I don't think of you as much of a comedian.
No, he does a lot of comedy.
You don't know that.
I do.
I've been getting a lot of work out of you.
I love their gourmet food shows.
I've been brainwashed by it.
One question about the wallet.
What's the first clue when you run out of bows?
The race is over and the first shot is open.
First love.
First love? First love?
Mm-hmm.
Come on, now, get your team, and if you guess right here, you get a four-point ticket.
Ticket.
Second one's open.
Romijuli.
Romijuri Romeo, Romeo, Juliet, answer me, please.
public
Romijulieautojuliette, yes.
I'm up to the third one, yoki open
First meeting
First meeting? Wait a minute.
Here he is. Come in.
Childhood friend.
Childhood friend, no.
Here we go to the end.
One hit.
One shot.
One shot!
What do you mean "one shot"?
I have no idea!
Okay, let's get you pumped.
The letters don't come out.
The moment you meet, you're married.
That's not a subject.
Of course not.
Well... we're married the moment we meet.
Five years and zero days old.
No, but that's...
No, that's not it.
I should have put something like "bibi-bibi" in there.
Like rice or something.
We could start with that, too.
I see.
Finally, the Mayu-Tan Association, which we haven't met yet.
The important first question is...
Associated word number one.
Ogawa
Drink bar
family restaurant
Correct answer
Yay!
Four points.
That's great.
It's a time play.
Can I still have everyone open this?
Drink bar
Children's Lunch
Drink bar for everyone except Ikeda
That's great!
No, four points here is huge.
Can you get a single word again in the association for every correct answer suddenly?
The first one is open!
Bamboo? Kaguyahime
Kaguyahime, no.
Now the last one.
Summer.
Summer of Bamboo.
Here you go.
"Somen" (fine white noodles)
That's right.
That's great!
I got the third one.
Three points!
I made every shot!
Niamura, that's great!
You're all doing great! Keep up the momentum of your high scores!
Hang in there, Maaitan! I'll do my best!
I did it when I was there! I've got momentum!
boo boo, Ichirose, open the first word in the associative word "Ichirose.
This one's black.
Sickle-cutter
me
Well, this one's a bit...
It's "kuromi" which means "sickle-cutter," and "poof!
Correct!
The last problem of the Association of Warriors by Association, and the winner?
The first clue of the last problem is
Justice.
Hero
No, it's not.
Now the other one
Cute heroes.
Sailor Moon
Oh, my God.
Amazing.
Amazing
Tedeasu!
Yay!
OK!
So the winner of the heated competition is
Malizan Church
Marizan Church
They were the overwhelming winners until the last game.
Well, they did it!
We did well... but I guess we had a strong team spirit...
It's a shame, but this is where we started. Two troublemakers, two troublemakers...
There's a lot of them. Yumiki's first photo book is on sale.
Tickets for the Tokyo leg of the Midsummer National Tour are on sale!
Who will win the position of Matsukuchi's companion?
This is Ayame Atsui. It has been getting hot lately and I would like to eat a lot of shaved ice.
I also hope to visit a shaved ice shop during the distribution.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Bye bye.